听好
Listen....
你们觉得我追得到吉宁吗
do you guys think I have a chance with Janine?
亲爱的  我们讨论过这件事了
Honey, we have been through this before!
对啊  别折磨自己了
Yeah. Don't do this to yourself.
她已经表示得很清楚  你们之间不可能
She's made it pretty clear; it is not going to happen.
那好吧  那我不该太兴奋
I guess I shouldn’t get too excited about the fact
因为我刚刚吻了她
that I just kissed her!
-真的假的  -太好了
- Are you serious? - That's great! Really?!
还得观察
Yeah, well, we'll see.
你居然吻了她
You kissed her?
吻得可火热了
We kissed it up real nice.
你吻了她  然后呢
So you kissed her, so what happened after that?
我就跑来告诉你们了
I came over here to tell you guys.
所以现在她在对面干等你啊
So she's waiting over there for you?
对
Yeah.
-我得走了  -好
- I gotta go. - Okay.
-我上舞蹈课要迟到了  -好
- I'm gonna be really late for dance class! - Okay.
-我真的要走了  -好吧
- Okay, now I'm really leaving. - All right.
但你可不可以...
But can you just...
把嘴唇留下来
...just leave your lips?
-再见  -再见
- Bye.  - Bye.
你们吻过她吗
Have you kissed her yet?
有够销魂的
It's awesome!
我怎么吻都吻不腻
I could do it forever.
她的吻功比我妈的厨艺还强
You know what? She kisses better than my mom cooks.
-幸好你说的是"厨艺"  -对啊
- I'm so glad you said, "cooks." - I know.
瑞秋  亲爱的
Oh hey Rachel, sweetheart?
你得通知邮局你搬家了
You have got to tell the post office that you have moved. Okay?
你的账单和信件  还是寄到我们这里来
We are still getting all your bills and stuff.
哇  陶瓷大谷仓
Oh-oh, Pottery Barn!
剩下的可以扔了
You can throw the rest away.
我不是你的清洁工
I'm not your garbage man.
我是你的邮差
I'm your mailman.
莫妮卡你看  快看快看
Monica, look. Look-look-look!
这里有我订的桌子
Here is that table that I ordered.
你是在陶瓷大谷仓买的
You got it from Pottery Barn?
对  这叫药师桌
Yeah. lt's an apothecary table.
有谁知道药师是什么吗
Does anyone even know what an apothecary is?
药剂师
A pharmacist.
"药剂师"
"A pharmacist."
瑞秋  菲比最讨厌陶瓷大谷仓了
Rach, Phoebe hates Pottery Barn.
我也讨厌陶瓷大谷仓
I hate Pottery Barn too.
我才在床上坐坐  就被赶出去了
They kicked me out just because I sat on a bed.
那是因为你脱了裤子钻进被子里
You took off your pants and climbed under the sheets.
我累了
I was tired.
菲比讨厌陶瓷大谷仓吗
Phoebe hates Pottery Barn?
大批量生产的东西她都讨厌
Yeah, she hates all mass produced stuff.
她认为家具都应该有历史  有典故
She thinks her furniture should have a history, a story behind it.
它是有典故啊
Well this has story behind it!
这桌子可是大老远从白原店运来的
I mean they had to ship it all the way from the White Plains store.
她喜欢独一无二的东西  比如像
It's gotta be one of a kind. You know like umm,
她柜台上那个丑到爆的水果陶碗吗
you know uh, what's that God awful ceramic fruit bowl she has on her counter?
那可是我做的
Hey! I made that for her.
-你会做陶瓷吗  -当然
- You made pottery? - Yeah.
我从垃圾堆捡来的水果碗做的
I made it out of a fruit bowl I found in the garbage.
相信我  你要是把桌子搬回家
I'm telling-If you put that in her apartment,
她肯定会抱怨不休的
you'll never hear the end of it.
好吧  我就说那是张古董药师桌
Okay fine! I'll-I'll just tell her it's an antique apothecary table,
她不必知道它的出处
She doesn't have to know where it came from.
我好喜欢这些小抽屉
I love these little drawers.
上面说可以放三百张CD呢
Oh, look! lt says that it holds 300 CDs.
正如往昔的药师桌一样
Just like the apothecary tables of yore.
然后农夫说
So the farmer says:
"那不是母牛  你也不是在挤奶"
"That's not a cow, and you're not milking."
你们能在一起真好
I am so glad you guys got together,
我和钱德勒一直希望有情侣朋友一起玩
Chandler and I are always looking for a couple to go out with
现在终于实现愿望了
and now we have one!
瞧  我们是成双又成对啊
Look at us, we're a couple of couples!
今晚真开心  那家餐厅好棒
I had so much fun tonight. What a great restaurant!
钱德勒  真不敢相信这次我让你请客
And, Chandler, I can't believe I let you pay for this one.
再次感谢
Thanks again, man.
你们明天要不要过来
So do you guys gonna come over tomorrow?
我来做我说的那种意大利面
I'll make that pasta thing I was telling you about.
-那太好了  -没事
- That'd be great! - Okay.
不过至少让我们带酒来吧
Oh, but hey look, at least let us bring the wine.
-乔伊  干嘛这么客气  -不行  我坚持
- Joey, you don't have to. - I insist.
-酒你会买吧  -会
- You'll get the wine, right? - Yeah.
-那就晚安咯  -明天见
- Okay, good night. - See you tomorrow.
好期待喔
Can't wait.
我们要怎么逃过这一劫呢
How are we going to get out of that one?
-什么  -我没办法连续应酬他们两晚
- What? - I can't handle two nights in a row with them.
莫妮卡和钱德勒有什么不好
What-what's wrong with Monica and Chandler?
不晓得  他们就是有点
I don't know, they're just a little...
爱说废话
...blah!
什么
Blah?
钱德勒爱说废话  莫妮卡则是
Well, you know, he's blah. She's just....
个子娇小  嗓门却很大
She's very loud for such a small person.
他们是我最要好的朋友
They're my best friends.
你的意思是我们不能一起玩吗
Are you saying we can't hang out with them?
那可就麻烦了
Because that'd be a problem.
不是  一起玩当然可以
No! Of course we can still hang out with them.
只要不是连续两晚就好
Just you know, not two nights in a row.
-可以吗  -可以吧
- Okay? - I guess.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果你乐意  你要我卖了朋友
If you want, I'll sell my friends
给你买礼物都行
and use the money to buy you presents.
好棒的桌子  在哪里买的
What a great table! Where did you get it?
你猜
Guess.
跳蚤市场
A flea market?
瞧  我就知道你会一猜就中
Ha! See, I knew, I knew you'd get it on the first guess.
很酷吧  这是药师桌
Isn't it cool? lt's an apothecary table.
他们就是把
You can just imagine that this is where...
药材存放在这里面
...they kept all their stuff to make potions.
-对吧  -对
- You know? - Yes.
你几乎还能闻到鸦片的味道
Ooh, you can almost smell the opium.
就是啊
Almost.
多少钱
How much was it?
才5百
Just only 500 bucks.
跳蚤市场居然卖到5百元
Five hundred bucks at a flea market?
我懂了  我以为你是问
Oh, okay see I thought, I thought you meant
全新时的价钱呢
how much was it when it was new,
-就是当时的价钱  -不是
- You know like back then. - No.
因为是跳蚤市场
Yeah no, I mean it was at a flea market,
所以差不多1块钱
so it was like a dollar.
-1块钱  -再加50元
- A dollar? - And 50?
所以总共51元
So it was like one and 50 dollars.
-他们按当年的价格折算  -对
- Ohh, okay, they gave you the old time pricing. - Yeah.
它是哪个年代的
Well, what period is it from?
往昔年代
It's from yore.
就是往昔的时代
Like the "days of yore," you know?
我知道
Yes, I do.
真是太完美了
God, it's just perfect.
它背后一定有一段很棒的典故
Wow! I bet it has a great story behind it too.
卖主有跟你说过它的出处之类的吗
Did they tell you anything? Like you know where it was from or...
有  这个我知道  它来自白原
Yes, that I know. This is from White Plains.
白原
White Plains.
真是一个充满魔力的地名
It sounds like such a magical place.
我们来了
- I'm here. - Hi!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
-你喜欢吗  -天啊
- You like it? - Oh, my God!
这是我的新药师桌
It's my new apothecary table!
罗斯  菲比就快到了
Ross, Phoebe is gonna be here any second.
不能让她看到这桌子
She can't see this.
为什么  她一定会喜欢
Why not? She'll love it.
这可是好东西
It's the real thing.
是在陶瓷大谷仓买的
I got it at Pottery Barn.
我知道  我也买了一张
I know you did! I bought the same one!
如果她看到你的桌子  就会知道我骗她
And if she sees your table she's gonna know that I lied to her.
因为我说我们的是原版
I said ours was an original.
你为什么这么说
Why did you do that?
因为她讨厌陶瓷大谷仓
Because she hates Pottery Barn.
她居然讨厌陶瓷大谷仓
She hates Pottery Barn?
我知道  我也很惊讶
I know! I know,
她说批量生产的东西  粗制滥造
She says it's all mass- produced nothing is authentic,
而且家家户户都有相同的东西
and everyone winds up having the same stuff.
快点  她随时会进来
So come on! she's gonna be here any second!
能不能拿个东西盖住它  拜托你了
Can we please just cover this up with something?! Please?
什么  我不要
What? No! No! I
我才不要对菲比遮遮掩掩的
I am not gonna hide it from Phoebe.
不过我在陶瓷大谷仓买了很漂亮的床单
Although I did get some great Pottery Barn sheets.
哎呀  我都忘了他们也有出床单
Oh, I forgot they made sheets!
真不敢相信她居然讨厌陶瓷大谷仓
I still can't believe she hates Pottery Barn.
罗斯  别念叨了  她又不是讨厌你
Ross, get over it! It's not like she hates you.
但讨厌陶瓷大谷仓也太...
Yeah, but Pottery Barn?
我觉得根本是她怪胎
You know what I think? She's just weird.
因为她是双胞胎  双胞胎都很怪
It's because she's a twin. Twins are weird.
她不是怪
Ross, she's not weird,
她只是希望她的东西独一无二
she just likes her stuff to be one of a kind.
什么最不独一无二  双胞胎
You know what's not one-of-a-kind? A twin!
菲比来了
Ooh, Phoebe's here!
让我们把灯关掉看电影吧
Okay, let's turn out all the lights and we'll just watch the movie!
-好漂亮的床单  -喜欢是吧
- Hey, cool sheet! - You like it?
-想知道哪里买的吗  -当然
- You want to know where I got it? - Sure.
他是在跳蚤市场买的
He got it at a flea market!
你居然在跳蚤市场买床单啊
You buy your sheets at a flea market?
罗斯  拜托  做人不能这么抠门
Ross come on, you gotta loosen the purse strings a little.
再过20分钟就开餐了  好兴奋喔
The dinner will be ready in 20 minutes. This is so exciting.
这是你今晚要带过来的那瓶酒
And here is the bottle of wine for you to bring over tonight.
你本来想送花给莫妮卡
You were also gonna buy Monica flowers...
却因为付了昨晚的饭钱  所以没钱买了
but you couldn't afford it, because you paid for dinner last night.
谢谢
Thanks. Thanks,
但其实今晚只有我一个人过去
but uh actually it's just gonna be me again tonight.
-吉宁怎么了  -她病得很重
- What happened to Janine? - She's, uh, really sick.
真糟糕
Oh that's too bad.
对啊  她整天都在房里
Yeah, she's been in there all day.
发高烧  又鼻塞
High fever, nose problem. lt's...
痰  痰  痰   痰  痰
...phlegm, phlegm, phlegm, phlegm, phlegm.
莫妮卡  钱德勒
Monica! Chandler!
今晚真非常非常抱歉
I'm really-really sorry about tonight.
不知道乔伊告诉你们了没
I don't know if Joey told you...
有出戏我一定得去看  抱歉
...but I couldn't get out of going to this play. I'm sorry.
-玩得开心点  -好
- Have a great time, huh? - Okay.
怪了  我不觉得有痰啊
That's funny, I saw no phlegm.
不  她真的病得很重
Oh, no, she really is sick.
那她为什么要去看戏
Then why is she going to a play?
感冒想退烧
Well, you know, "Starve a fever...
就要去看戏
...go to a play for a cold."
乔伊  吉宁为什么不来吃饭
Joey, why is Janine not coming over for dinner?
她不想连续两晚都跟你们玩
She didn't want to hang out with you guys two nights in a row.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
她为什么不想跟我们玩
Why doesn't she want to hang out with us?
因为她觉得你很爱说废话
Because she uh, she-she thinks that you are blah
而你  莫妮卡你的嗓门太大
and that you, and that you, Monica, are too loud.
什么
What?!
What?
所以她昨晚只是假装开心咯
So she was just pretending to have a good time last night?
她居然当面骗我们
She was lying to our faces?
太扯了  她凭什么批评我们
I can't believe this. Who is she to judge us?
我们对她多好
We couldn't have been nicer to her.
我才不爱说废话  我是谈笑风生
And I am not blah. I am a hoot!
拜托  你们大人有大量  别生气
Come on, please, please, you guys. Don't be mad.
她之所以这么说
I'm sure she just, she just said that stuff
一定是因为她紧张
...because she was nervous
因为你们是我最要好的朋友
because you guys are like my best friends.
我们又是第一次约会
And it was our first date.
而且她病得很重嘛
Plus, she's really sick.
-你刚明明说那是假的  -我知道
- No, you sh-No you said you made that up!! - I know,
但你不觉得生病这个借口
I know, but don't you think the sick thing
比看戏好吗
is way better than the play thing?
都很好
They're both good.
我通常都说"莫妮卡又醉了"
I generally just go with, "Monica's drunk again."
你们大人不记小人过
Come on you guys, come on please
拜托再给她一次机会吧
please just give her another chance.
她会经常过去的  我保证
She'll come around, I promise.
当然好
Of course we will.
-回去做晚饭吧  -好
- Come on, we gotta make dinner. - Okay.
我不喜欢那个女人
I do not like that woman!
我听得见
I can hear you!
我的嗓门真的很大
I am loud!
菲比  别把脚翘在我的新...
Hey Pheebs, Could you please not put your feet up on my new...
旧床单上
Old sheet.
好
Oh, sure.
我的药师桌
My apothecary table!
-什么  -不
- What? - No!
罗斯  这张桌子是哪里买的
Ross, where did you get this?
陶瓷大谷仓  行吗
I got it at Pottery Barn, okay?
我的老天
Oh, my God!
菲比  陶瓷大谷仓抄袭我们古董桌的设计
Phoebe, Pottery Barn has ripped off the design of our antique!
天啊  要是他们是抄袭我们的桌子
Oh my God, if they've ripped off our table
那张桌子一定不只值51元
ours must be much more than one and fifty dollars!
这张连鸦片的味道都没有
Well this doesn't even smell like opium.
当然没有  只有你洒出去的酒味
Of course not, it smells like wine, which you spilled!
谢谢你还顺便毁了我的床单
And thanks for wrecking my sheet by the way.
罗斯  别激动
Ross, calm down.
我赔你八十美分就是了
I'll give you the 80 cents.
再来一次
Okay, one more time.
钱德勒  你还要柳橙汁吗
Would you like some more orange juice?
-音量刚刚好  -就是啊
- Perfect decibel. - I know!
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
没什么  就是聊天说点废话啥的
Nothing. We're just talking. You know, blah- blah- blah.
别这样  你们说过要尽力的
Look, come on you guys, you said you were gonna try!
好吧  我是过来邀请你们
All right look, I came over here
跟我和吉宁一起去看电影
to invite you to a movie with me and Janine.
-你们觉得呢  -非常乐意
- What do you say? - I'd like to...
但是我不确定有没有空
...but I'm not sure if we have the time.
真好笑...我也很无奈
Very funny. I don't know what to do.
我真的很希望你们能处得来
I really want you guys to get along.
拜托你们跟我们去吧
Just please come to the movie with us.
这是你们欠我的
You owe me.
-我们欠你的  -没错
- We owe you? - That's right.
你们刚开始交往时  我可是帮了你们不少忙
I helped you guys out a lot in the start of your relationship.
我帮你们偷偷交往了半年
I helped you sneak around for six months.
跟白痴一样
I looked like an idiot.
我觉得很丢脸
And I was humiliated.
还只挣了两百元
And I only made $200.
我们没有给你一分钱
We didn't give you any money.
你以为我不知道吗
You don't think I know that?
我不知道该拿它
See? I can't decide whether it would go better
配巫师餐椅
next to the new wicker dining chair,
撒哈拉书桌
...the Sahara desk...
还是派克饭桌
...or the Parker console table.
这里相当于小型陶瓷大谷仓了
I didn't know there was a Pottery Barn up here.
-我知道  我有点买疯了  -才有点吗
- I know,  I know, I went a little crazy. - A little?
你的屋子就跟产品目录第七十二页差不多
Your place looks like page 72 of the catalogue.
看这个
Look at that!
装饰鸟笼  大号的
The ornamental birdcage! Large.
罗斯  小心  那个很旧
Oh, Ross? Be careful. That is very old.
殖民地时代早期的鸟商
Early Colonial bird merchants used to
都用它带鸟上市场
bring their birds to market in that.
有意思
Fascinating.
又一个惊人的发现
Another amazing find!
-它一定也有很棒的典故  -没错
- I bet this has a great story too. - lt does. lt does.
这是殖民地时期分隔房间的装置
It is a room-separating apparatus from Colonial times.
有好多东西都来自殖民地时期
A lot of this stuff is from the Colonial times.
能列举几个其他时期的名称吗  瑞秋
What are some other time periods, Rachel?
有往昔时期
Well, there's yore.
还有昨年时期
And, you know, yesteryear.
瑞秋对这种东西真的很有眼光
Yeah no, I'm telling you Rachel has such a good eye for this stuff.
罗斯  如果你家要重新布置
Ross, if you ever decide to redecorate...
而且我觉得很有必要
...and I think you should...
你应该找瑞秋帮忙
...you should ask Rachel to help.
亲爱的  他才不需要我的帮忙
Oh honey he doesn't need my help.
拜托  他早该扔掉那些...
Oh, come on! I think he's ready to get rid of,
你怎么称呼来着
What did you call it?
"便宜山寨货  恐龙时期的垃圾"
The "cheap knockoffs and dinosaur junk"?
真的吗
Really?
你知道吗
You know what,
既然你这么清楚我的需求
since you have such a great sense of what I need- -
我这里有六十元
Here's 60 bucks.
你带着菲比  去殖民时期的跳蚤市场
Why don't you take Phoebe down to that Colonial flea market
帮我买几件家具吧
...and get me some stuff.
其实  我觉得菲比不会想去
You know what? I don't, I don't really think Phoebe wants to come.
-不  我想去  -她想去
- No, I do want to. - She does want to.
-她想去  -没错
- She does want to. - Yeah!
菲比  我真不知道说什么
Pheebs, I don't know what to say.
上次跳蚤市场的好东西比较多
I guess the flea market was just better last time.
-至少我帮罗斯买了床单  -没错
- Well, at least I got these sheets for Ross. - Yeah.
瞧  是陶瓷大谷仓
Look at this. Pottery Barn.
别看了
You know what? Don't look at it.
-真的  别看了  -快看
- Seriously, don't look at it. - Look!
你看  他们抄袭我们的咖啡桌
There's the table they stole from us.
这些混蛋
Those bastards!
我们走
Let's go.
那台电风扇跟我们的有点像
That fan kind of looks like ours
还有那个鸟笼和...
and the birdcage and....
这根本就是我们的客厅
Wait a second, this is our exact living room!
不  才不是呢  不一样啦
No! No! No! No it's not! No it's not!
拜托  我们的完全不一样
Come on! Phoebe, ours is totally different!
我们没有...我们没有那盏灯
I mean, we don't have the-- We don't have that lamp.
还有那扇隔板是在另一边
And that screen is, you know,on the other side.
我的老天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我们家具都是在这里买的
This is where you got all our stuff.
陶瓷大谷仓  我的天啊
Pottery Barn! Oh, my God!
好吧  好吧  你说对了  对不起
Okay! Okay-okay look-no I did, I'm sorry ,
菲比  我想要这些东西
Phoebe, I wanted this stuff.
又知道你讨厌陶瓷大谷仓
And I know how you feel about Pottery Barn.
-别气了  -可我就是生气  我气死了
- Come on, don't be mad. - No-no-no, but I am mad! I am mad!
这些东西就是现在社会的问题
Because this stuff is everything that is wrong with the world!
而他们都在我家客厅摆着
And it's all sitting up in my living room
但我却只想着我没有那盏灯
and all I can think about is how I don't have that lamp!
那就买下那盏灯
Well, then, honey, buy the lamp.
我们有罗斯给的六十元
We have that 60 bucks from Ross.
不可以  不可以
I can't! I can't!
除非...
Unless....
你是说我不买那盏灯  你就要搬走吗
Are you saying you'd move out if I didn't buy that lamp?
不  我不会搬走
No, I'm not gonna move out!
你是说我不买那盏灯
But are you saying that you would move out
你就要搬走吗
if I didn't buy that lamp?
没错  我一定会搬走
Yes! I would so move out.
那我别无选择
Okay, then I don't have a choice.
-唯有买下那盏灯  -没错
- I have to buy that lamp! - That's right.
不过至少那张药师桌是真的古董
But at least the apothecary table's real.
太棒了
Well, this-this-this was great.
大家都很尽兴吧
Didn't everybody have a great time?
我很尽兴  真的
I did. I really did.
两位  我在这道个歉
And you guys, I've got to say, I'm sorry
上次聚会后我态度怪怪的
if I was weird after the last time we went out.
可能是紧张或什么的吧
I guess I was just nervous or something.
-我们完全理解  -对啊  别放在心上
- That's understandable. - Yeah, Don't worry about it.
-所以我们可以再出去吗  -可以啊
- So we can go out again? - Yeah
-当然可以  -好的
- Absolutely. - Okay.
-那晚安咯  -晚安
- Well, goodnight. - Goodnight.
看吧
See?
很开心吧
Wasn't that fun?
我们非搬家不可
We have got to move.
什么
What?
我就知道
I knew it!
你的嗓门也不小  死丫头
You know, you're not so quiet yourself, missy!
我爱说废话
I'm blah?
比看现代舞更无聊的
The only thing more boring than watching modern dance
就是听你聊现代舞
is having to listen to you talk about it,
"钱德勒  我刚才浑然忘我了"
"Oh, Chandler, I just lost myself in the movement."
我知道你是在说话
You know, I know you're talking...
但我只听到"叽哩呱啦叽哩呱啦"
...but all I hear is, "Blah-blah-blah-blah-blah."
你和我  现在就出去决胜负
All right, you and me! Let's go right now!
好了  够了
All right! All right! Enough!
够了  你们回去
Enough! Enough!! Enough! You two, go home.
我要跟吉宁谈一谈
I gotta talk to Janine.
你绝对可以撂倒她
I really think you could take her.
别让我在走廊上碰到你
You better hope I don't see you in the hallway!
好了
All right.
我们有个小小的问题
Look, we got a little bit of a problem here.
他们是我的朋友  你不能对他们无礼
These people are my friends; you can't treat them that way.
他们也对我出言不逊
They said stuff to me too.
我知道  我会找他们谈的
I know! I know! And I'm going to talk to them about it.
他们对我很重要
They mean so much to me.
就像我的家人
They're like my family, you know?
如果你们一见面就吵  我...
If you guys are gonna be fighting all the time, I....
我们就不能在一起
I don't think we can be together.
这是行不通的
It just can't work, okay?
那不行
It can't.
我很不开心
I'm very upset.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
要是我过去道歉呢  这样行吗
Would, would it help if I went over and apologized?
好
Yeah! Yeah!
这样一定行
That would be very helpful! Yeah.
我刚说在走廊上碰到会怎样
What did I tell you about the hall?
我只是要过来  为我的言行向你们道歉
I was coming over to apologize for my behavior.
我很希望能跟你们做朋友
I'd really like it if we could be friends.
我知道那样乔伊会很高兴  所以
Well, I know that would make Joey happy, so...
我也愿意
...l would like that too.
-太好了  -来吧
- Great. - Now, come on.
-很高兴能达成共识  -我也是
- I'm glad we worked it out. - Me too.
-回头见  -再见
- I'll see you. - Bye.
-不见也能听着  -够了  死孩子  开战
- Or I'll hear you. - That's it, big girl! Come on!
慢着
Wait!
你最好快逃
You'd better run!
-你听见了吗  -听见了
- Did you hear that? - Yeah.
-我该怎么办  -我也不知道  难为你了
- What am I gonna do? - Yeah, I don't know, I'm sorry man.
-要去看吗  -当然
- You Want to go watch? - Yeah!
-你们好  -她搬出去了吗
- How you doing? - So did she move out?
差不多了
Pretty much.
你居然就这样跟她分手了
I cannot believe you broke up with her just like that.
不适合就是不适合
When it's not right, you know it.
-你还好吗  -没事  还好
- You okay? - Yeah! Yeah. I'll be all right.
-我有办法让你开心  -什么办法
- You know what would cheer you up? - What?
我明天晚上
I'm giving this lecture
有一个关于地形侵蚀理论的讲座
on erosion theories tomorrow night.
你应该来听
I think you should come.
你说得对  我确实开心多了
You're right, that did cheer me up.